(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-20T01:35:54.498909",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Ring a, ring a, roses, fa-la-la, round and round,
fa-la-la, fa-la-la, up and down, fa-la-la, here...
Hey! Aren't you here early?
Wait, or perhaps am I late?
Welcome to my 3D Showcase, everyone!
Thank you for showing up right on time! I'm ready, I promise, I'm ready.
We have a lot of fun stuff planned for today.
It means a lot to me that you came to see me.
Here I am, in 3D, for you!
I have a lot to show off today,
including myself, but also this beautiful...
...forest, which I call home, which I can finally show to you!
I'm excited!
And if you're also excited, and you want to talk about the stream, feel free to post with the hashtag #3DKirin,
which you can see on the screen somewhere!
And while I'm here for you in 3D, do you have any...
...pose requests you would like to see from me?
I'm taking your requests right now, so you better get them in while you can!
What do you think? What do you think?
I'm in a generous mood right now. I just might even...
...do the splits for you.
Don't think I forgot! I remember, I remember!
You want to see?
Okay, I said I was generous, but, but am I really so generous?
I don't know, splits... Is there a way to do the splits in a ladylike manner?
Well, there's two methods. You can go this way, that's more of a lunge...
...or you can go this way.
Maybe, maybe we scrap that one.
Do you have any idol-like pose requests for me?
Mermaid pose? No. I'm not doing mermaid pose.
No mermaid pose.
A slap? You want to be slapped?
I shouldn't be surprised at this point.
All right, come here! Come here!
Pucha!
You want another one? You want another one? That wasn't enough for you?
All right, all right, I think that was enough of that.
Let me show you around a little bit. Hopefully you're not too, too dazed...
...from the slaps.
We have, in my lovely forest...
...many features, such as...
...a fountain, perfect ASMR ambiance,
lots of bubbles.
Not only do we have a fountain, well, first of all,
there's so many beautiful flowers around, and this giant tree, the World Tree...
...has finally been completed!
I built it. I built it myself. I did that. I'm Nature, I did that.
We also have a bench,
beautiful feature,
and a gazebo!
How many hit points do you think this thing has?
I bet it wouldn't even flinch if I hit it with an arrow.
Very scary.
But...
I think I'm not the only one in this forest.
Could it be?
Namu! Come out, come out, wherever you are.
Are you sleeping again, Namu?
She's cute! She's cute! She's really cute!
Look at you, Namu! Just look at you! Oh.
Hey, where are you going?
Hey, I'm trying to pet you.
Where are you off to?
It's my 3D showcase, not yours.
Don't get a big head. You know I'm the real Keeper of Nature, right?
Where are you going? Where are you going?
Are you... Are you really just going to go to sleep?
Like this?
During my 3D showcase? I guess I shouldn't be surprised at this point.
Do we have anybody else here in this forest?
Could it be? There's many fully grown trees around, but...
Sapling? Is that you?
Wait, but... But you're looking a little bit different. What happened to you?
Aren't you supposed to have a sprout?
Usually, you're calling me bald, but today, you're the one who's bald.
Oh no, no, no, don't look so sad. I'm sorry, I'm sorry. Don't be so sad. Come here.
Come here. There, there. There, there. I will love you even if you're bald.
Oh!
Incredible! Is this the power of nature?
No, you probably did this all on your own. You're pretty incredible too, you know.
All right, Sapling. Why don't we sit you down right here?
It's your 3D showcase, too! Look at you go! Aren't you awfully cute?
Let me guess. That's not your preferred seat.
This must be your preferred seat!
So cute! So cute!
What a cute 3D form you have! Look how boing-boing!
I feel like I'm getting shown up a little bit on my own debut.
First we have Namu looking especially cute, and now we have boing-boing Sapling.
I'm very cute, too, right?
Well, thank you very much for coming, and this is not all we have.
Did you think I was really going to come here and just talk to you for an hour straight?
Well, that is something that I would do, but...
We have lots planned for today.
So please stay tuned and enjoy! And...
Let's go ahead and get started, shall we? Woo!
I'm back! Hello!
For our first section, I would like to call some friends in.
Hello? Hello, friends? Are you here?
Friends here! Friends here! Friends here!
Hello!
Fauna! You're so cute! You are here! Welcome, welcome!
Oh, thank you!
Thank you for coming to my 3D showcase. I wanted to have you guys here.
And who might you be? Would you like to introduce yourselves, starting over over here with IRyS?
All righty! Hi, rys! It's IRyS from Hololive English with the fellow lovely ladies, like usual. Let's go!
Welcome, welcome!
You're looking so cute! Glowing!
And next we have...
What's up? It's Baelz Hakos from Hololive English. Pnya-cat!
So cute!
And next... who is this?
Ooh, konnichiwa! It's Ouro Kronii from Hololive English Council, and you are so 3D!
I am!
And so dynamic! Look at that 360!
So much movement!
Oh my god! Look at those sleeves defying gravity!
Thank you! And up next we have...
Oh, hi! I'm...
...Nanashi Mumei!
Fauna, you're so cute!
Thank you!
Oh my god, thank you!
Well, since I am in 3D, I wondered if you guys had any requests for me?
Poses or actions that you can only get...
...right now...
...when I can move like this?
Poses? What should we ask for?
Do you have one, Mumei?
Do you have an idea?
I have an idea.
Okay, not so much a pose, more of an action.
More of an acting action.
Could you pretend that you're in a Category 5 hurricane?
Let's go!
Okay, like outside, not in a shelter?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, like outside.
Reporting it.
She blew away! She blew away!
I guess I should be screaming.
Amazing!
How was my acting?
I think it was amazing.
Very convincing.
Thank you, thank you!
Who's next? Who's next?
What you got?
I want you to pretend that you are a Category 5 hurricane.
Okay, okay.
Is this part of a tornado?
Is this a tornado? It is similar to a tornado.
I have water!
Amazing!
Thank you!
Getting dizzy!
I have one!
You have one? Okay.
Are you gonna go easy on me?
What if you were a tree in a Category 5 hurricane?
It keeps going!
Okay.
So wavy.
Don't break yourself!
Stem, trunk...
My branch fell off.
She lost a branch! She lost a branch! No!
Wait, I was thinking of asking for a pose that had nothing to do with a Category 5 hurricane.
That's fine.
But everyone's asking for a Category 5 hurricane...
...thing, so...
I was originally gonna ask for a newborn baby pose, cause you're always, you know, mommy...
But instead I'm going to ask for a newborn baby in a...
...Category 5 hurricane!
Even the sound effects! Oh my god!
Thank you, thank you!
That baby's kind of strong!
Yeah, baby... We can't have baby getting into trouble.
But I did not bring you here just for Category 5 hurricanes!
I also would like to play a little game.
It is a 3D showcase classic...
...Charades!
Yay!
Oh, charades!
Yeah, so I'll be pantomiming various words which I do not know,
and they will have one minute to guess.
And that's pretty much it. Everybody knows charades, right?
So, let's start the first word!
Only sillies don't know.
First word.
Is this a group effort or individual effort?
Huh?
What?
She's pointing up. She's pointing up, and then...
Now she's...
Is it two words? Two words.
Are you a plant?
A tree?
It's tall. It's tall and short. Middle?
She's...
Oh, evolution!
Evolution!
Nature! Nature!
Dancing? Is she dancing?
She's a baby!
Baby getting into trouble!
And then the mother... Talks to the hand.
Talk to the hand?
Stepdaughter?
Stepmother?
She's crying, she's crying. Someone's crying, okay.
She's so sad.
Oh my gosh, what is...
I can't get hurricane out of my mind, I'm sorry.
I keep seeing hurricane!
All right, time's up!
The word was "Teenager"!
Oh!
That was a hard one!
That was extremely hard!
Is it teenager height?
I was trying to go for height,
and then I was trying to go like baby into kid into teenager,
that's like the "Don't talk to me..."
"Don't talk to me, mom!"
I thought it was like a seed or a plant...
I was gonna say "maid" until the "don't talk to me", "talk to the hand" thing.
Evolution was kind of... Not really.
Evolution...
All right. Next word!
Next one!
Uh-oh.
Horse racing! Horse racing! Horse race!
Yes! You got it!
That one was a little easier. Good job.
Easy. Uh-huh.
All right, up next.
Okay.
Swimming! Swimming! Swimming?
Huh? Is she getting the water out of the way? What?
I don't think that's what she's doing.
Pebble throwing. She's putting...
She's putting stuff... She's spreading... Is she cooking? Cooking!
Kneading dough! Kneading dough! Baking!
Oh wait, she's dead! Oh, she dead.
Oh, she's... Yeah, she's dying there. Wait.
Did she get stabbed? Stabbed! She got stabbed! Spilling out...
Her blanket's too hot while she's sleeping.
Oh, is she pregnant? Is she throwing it away?
Infant! What? Throwing... Surgery! Surgery!
Surgery! Surgery! It was surgery!
That was surgery?
Good job! Oh, what was the swimming at the beginning?
These are difficult words! All right, next up.
Huh?
A wig!
Oh, she's sneaking. She's sneaking. Bald Fauna playing Hitman. Hitman, Hitman.
Oh, hit... No?
Assassin! Assassin! Oh, is it Matrix?
Yes! Assassin! It was assassination! Close!
Close enough!
I mean, technically, was I wrong? Not really.
No, I... The mods'll allow it.
All right. It was close enough. Next, next word.
Chicken! A chicken!
Chicken bird. Bird.
Bird. Peacock! Big bird.
Peacock? Rooster? Rooster?
Bigger bird. An ostrich, ostrich!
Emu.
Did she say emu? Oh my god.
They're so cute. Oh, she's eating now. She's...
Chicken. Is it... It's delicious, then. Um... Turkey! Yes! Turkey!
Turkey!
Good job, good job!
Did you say emu again? Wait, were you eating the turkey?
Eating the turkey? Well, how else am I supposed to show it?
Aww, Fauna!
Uh, next question!
Oh, down on the ground. Oh, baby! Baby!
Baby, she's a mom, she's a mom.
Rock-a-bye baby. Babysitter?
Oh, yes! Babysitter!
That was so fast! On the ground? What?
Babysitter. You've got to treat your baby nicer.
Yeah, I don't know why they left the baby on the ground.
Leave it back there. New parenting hack!
New parenting hack? Yeah.
That just don't allow the baby to hit the... Category 5 hurricane.
Got to be careful in case of natural disasters.
Hey, keep it in the house, that's what you're supposed to do. A natural disaster?
You measure the most beautiful natural disaster.
Oh, thank you.
I mean, she... she truly is making my heart go all over the place.
Doki doki. Doki doki.
You're so cute! Oh, thank you!
All right, next question.
Next one, next one. Next, next, next.
Salt and pepper! Salt! Salt! Cooking!
Cooking! Cooking! She's got the salt. Spice.
Bowl. Spice. Curry. Shaker!
Salt shaker! Salt shaker!
Oh! Salt shaker.
Salt shaker, specifically.
I see, I see. You see?
I see.
All right, thank you guys for joining me!
I appreciate you being here to celebrate with me.
Thank you, thank you!
You're the goddess of the forest! Thank you! This is my forest now!
Oh my god!
Oh, can we eat tea together? Yes!
...eat crumpets, haha!
We can have a tea party together, yes please!
In the gazebo? In the gazebo!
Well, thank you for joining me! And up next, I will be...
...perhaps doing some performances?
You stay tuned!
Thank you! Bye-bye!
Bye-bye! Thank you guys!
語れない 眠れない トロイメライ
I can't talk about it, I can't sleep, a Träumerei
あなたの見ている症状
The symptoms you are seeing
誰も読めないカルテ
A medical chart that no one can read
不可思議 知りたいだけ
Mysterious, I just want to know
嘘も 現実も
Lies and reality
どちらも
Both of them
真実だったの
Were the truth
本当よ
It's true
今日も ひとりごと
Today again, talking to myself
何も 無理をしないで
Without forcing anything
わたし 愛されたい
I want to be loved
うやむや サヨナラ 軽い眩暈
Vague goodbyes, a light dizziness
あなたのいない現象界
The phenomenal world without you
誰も読めないカルテ
A medical chart that no one can read
自意識 溢れ出して
Self-consciousness overflowing
鼓動 世界像
My heartbeat, the image of the world
いつも 噛み合わないの
Are never in sync
痛くて
It hurts so much
迷い 願い事
Wandering, making wishes
何も 疑わないで
Without doubting anything
混ざり 溶け合いたい
I want to blend and melt together
可愛いくない 分からない 理由存在
Uncute, incomprehensible, reasons and existence
あなたと残す後悔
Regrets left behind with you
誰も読めないカルテ
A medical chart that no one can read
不愉快 繰り返して
Repeating discomfort
正しい夢は
Correct dreams
哀しい声は
Sad voices
美しい 疑わしい
Beautiful, suspicious
羨ましいね どれ？
Envious, right? Which one?
語れない 眠れない トロイメライ
I can't talk about it, I can't sleep, a Träumerei
あなたの見ている症状
The symptoms you are seeing
誰も読めないカルテ
A medical chart that no one can read
不可思議 知りたいだけ
Mysterious, I just want to know
終わらない 事はない トロイメライ
There's nothing that doesn't end, a Träumerei
あなたとまた行く境界
Heading again to the boundary with you
誰も読めないカルテ
A medical chart that no one can read
思春期 傷口 胸のうち
Adolescence, wounds, deep within the heart
不可思議 知りたいだけ
Mysterious, I just want to know
あー！わため先輩！
Ah! Watame-senpai!
イエーイ！可愛いー！ありがとう！
Yay! So cute! Thank you!
This was my first guest of my 3D showcase, my beloved senpai, Watame-senpai!
イエーイ！
Yay!
ホロライブJP4期生、ホロライブEN1期生...
Hololive JP 4th Gen, Hololive EN 1st Gen...
角巻わためでーす！
I'm Tsunomaki Watame!
Thank you for coming to my forest! What do you think of the stage?
すごーい！Very beautiful place!
Amazing! Very beautiful place!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
Wow! お、Fauna's house?
Wow! Oh, Fauna's house?
My house!
Oh, Fauna's house! Very big! Very big な！
Oh, Fauna's house! Very big! Very big, huh!
Do you want to go? 行きますか？
Do you want to go? Shall we go?
Let's go!
We have... We have a show...
あ、ダメか、ダメか。そっか。じゃ、後で！After!
Ah, we can't? We can't. I see. Then later! After!
後で！
Later!
Yeah, very... Cute 3Dだよ！可愛い！
Yeah, very... It's cute 3D! Cute!
可愛い！
Cute!
背同じ色ね！ピンク、ピンク... と、白！白！White!
We have similar outfit colors! Pink, pink... and white! White! White!
ね！同じ！同じ！
Right! Same! Same!
Dressね！可愛い！
The dresses! Cute!
可愛い！Big face, small face...
Cute! Big face, small face...
いいえ！
No!
可愛い！可愛い！可愛い！可愛い！と、
Cute! Cute! Cute! Cute! And...
キリン！
Kirin!
Sheep, Kirin.
可愛い〜！
So cute!
何何何何！ラム、ラム！
What, what, what, what! Lamb, lamb!
これこれこれ！
Hey, hey, hey!
一緒に歌ってくれてありがとう！
Thank you for singing with me!
こちらこそありがとう！また歌いましょう！
Thank you as well! Let's sing together again!
はい！頑張ってね！ありがとう！またね！
Yes! Good luck! Thank you! See you!
Ooh... I feel healed already. Fuwafuwa-senpai, she's so cute!
That was just our first guest, though. And I think we have one more on the way... Doesn't something smell a little fishy to you?
もうそう♡えくすぷれす
[Song: Mousou Express]
妄想がね 暴走する ちょっとお急ぎに
My wild delusions are running wild, speeding ahead a little
飛び乗って 今 会いに行きたいの
I want to hop aboard right now and go see you
言い訳とか 理由だとか めんどくさいな
Excuses and reasons are such a hassle
運命だから 仕方がないよね
It's destiny, so it can't be helped, right?
叶わなければ この恋は
As long as it doesn't come true, this love
永遠に 冷めることもないの
Will never ever cool down
何も知らない 瞳閉じて
Knowing nothing, closing my eyes
可愛いままで 居たかったんだ
I just wanted to stay cute
思い通りにならない 世界ならもういらない
If it's a world where things don't go my way, I don't need it anymore
欲しいのは ひとつだけ 全部 全部 全部
There's only one thing I want, all, all, all of it
思い通りにならない 世界とかいらない
A world that doesn't go as I wish is useless to me
欲しいのは ひとつだけ 全部 全部 全部 全部
There's only one thing I want, all, all, all, all of it
この気持ちは この気持ちにしかなれないのに
These feelings can only ever be these feelings
みんな勝手に 決めつけ過ぎだし
Yet everyone assumes things far too much on their own
知らないくせ 知ったふりで そんな簡単に
Pretending to know when you don't, giving up so easily like that
諦めちゃうの もったいないよね
Is such a waste, isn't it?
叶わなければ この夢は
As long as it doesn't come true, this dream
永遠に 冷めることもないの
Will never ever fade away
何も知らない 瞳閉じて
Knowing nothing, closing my eyes
可愛いままで 居たかったんだ
I just wanted to stay cute
思い通りにならない 世界ならもういらない
If it's a world where things don't go my way, I don't need it anymore
いいえなら　もういらない
If it's a "no", I don't need it anymore.
欲しいのは　ひとつだけ
There's only one thing I want,
せんぶ　せんぶ　せんぶ　せんぶ
all of it, all of it, all of it, all of it.
思い通りに　ならない
If a world doesn't go the way I want,
世界なら　もういらない
I don't need it anymore.
欲しいのは　ひとつだけ
There's only one thing I want,
せんぶ　せんぶ　せんぶ　せんぶ
all of it, all of it, all of it, all of it.
All of it, all of it, all of it, all of it.
せんぶ
All of it.
叶わないければ
If it doesn't come true...
この恋は　永遠に冷めることもないの
this love will never cool down for eternity.
何も知らない　瞳をとじて
Knowing nothing, close your eyes...
かわいいままで　欲しかったのかな
and stay cute, was that what you wanted?
思い通りに　ならない
If a world doesn't go the way I want,
世界なら　もういらない
I don't need it anymore.
欲しいのは　ひとつだけ
There's only one thing I want,
せんぶ　せんぶ　せんぶ　せんぶ
all of it, all of it, all of it, all of it.
思い通りに　ならない
If a world doesn't go the way I want,
世界とかいらない
I don't need a world like that.
欲しいのは　ひとつだけ
There's only one thing I want,
せんぶ　せんぶ　せんぶ　せんぶ
all of it, all of it, all of it, all of it.
ららら...
La la la...
ららら... せんぶ　せんぶ　せんぶ　せんぶ
La la la... All of it, all of it, all of it, all of it.
ららら...
La la la...
ららら... せんぶ　せんぶ　せんぶ
La la la... All of it, all of it, all of it.
ドキドキ
Pit-a-pat...
Mm, is there someone hiding over there?
You don't have to be shy. Come on over, take a seat.
You didn't think you could enter my forest without being invited for a cup of tea, did you?
Come on, scoot closer. Have a sip. It won't hurt, I promise.
Hey, you. You're finally awake.
You were trying to enter the forest, right?
Walked right into my tea party,
same as all the other saplings in this forest.
That was your first mistake.
Us herbal tea tenders have a hard time leaving afterwards.
Speaking of leaves... look at you. You've already sprouted yours.
You're growing into a wonderful little sapling already.
My tea is pretty potent, huh?
Don't worry, little sapling. You'll come around to life with nature.
You can leave all of your human worries behind.
Civilization, society, work...
None of that matters when you're a tree.
I'll take good care of you here.
And it looks like you do need some care.
Your freshly sprouted leaves need some attention.
Here, here. Let me get some tools.
Hmm, what should I use on you?
Let me check my box.
Syringe? No.
Wrench? Mm...
Banana? Maybe.
Scalpel? Mm...
No, scissors would be better.
Ah, I'll just grab whatever.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
What's that look for?
Oh, worried about these?
You know I wouldn't hurt you.
I just need to prune some of your leaves.
I would tell you to stay still, but... you don't have much of a choice like this.
Yeah, yeah... this one?
And this one?
There! Doesn't that feel better?
I'm sure all those extra leaves were weighing you down.
Aww, what about... this one?
Uh-oh, maybe... that one was important?
Uh-oh, don't worry about that, little Sapling. It'll grow back!
Uh, let's... move on here...
I will use this brush to clean your leaves...
...the remaining leaves, I guess.
Yoshi, yoshi... Yoshi, yoshi...
There, there... There, there...
There, there...
I'll accept you, even if you lose all of your leaves.
As Master Fauna, I'll provide you with the nutrients you're no longer able to create through photosynthesis.
Yoshi, yoshi...
There, there...
Looks good.
Now, if you want to grow those leaves back...
I think you'll need some water!
Ah, but not too much, don't want those roots to rot away!
There! With care like this, you'll want to stay in the forest forever, right?
Now, let me just get you one more thing...
Hey! Where are you looking? Don't even think about it!
Here, here, have a bite of this!
I'm sorry for hitting you with a book!
Oh, there, there! There, there! You'll be okay!
Come on, I need you on nice and normal vibes so you can watch the rest of my showcase, okay?
神様の神様
[Title: God of Gods]
一体この世はどうなって居るのかな
I wonder what in the world is happening to this world?
私の空を飛び越えて 地球の周りをくるくると
Flying over my sky, spinning round and round the Earth...
月火水木金土日に 繰り返すこのバイオリズム
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Saturday, Sunday, this repeating biorhythm...
全人類の選択肢 みたいなテスト
A test like options for all mankind...
So I'm just spinning around, around, around the world
好き 嫌いがない ない ないから
Because there is no "like" or "dislike", none at all...
Spinning around, around, around the world
大気にもどかしい 思い 伝えたいから
Because I want to convey my frustrating feelings to the atmosphere...
最近どんなのって言われや
When asked "How have you been lately?"
"I'm fine, thank you" だっていえるでしょ
I can say "I'm fine, thank you", right?
ぐんぐん手頃になる私を
As I rapidly become more manageable,
そっとそばに来て光って
gently come close to me and shine.
愛した時から 私が神様
From the moment I loved you, I became a god.
さあ あなたの言う通りに
Now then, just as you say,
の... 成り上がり 歴史は去れど 繰り返す
rising up, though history passes, it repeats itself.
初めと終わりが変わる景色
Scenery where the beginning and end change.
風船 膨らませ 膨らませ
Inflate the balloons, inflate them...
巡り巡るよ この季節に
Round and round in this season,
全知と全能 この手にして
grabbing omniscience and omnipotence with these hands.
I'm just spinning around, around, around, around the world
好きにしてもいい？
Can I do whatever I want?
いい？ いい？ いいかな？
Is it okay? Is it okay? Is it really okay?
欲しいもの叶い... 叶い... 叶わないなら
If my wishes can't come... can't come... true,
それじゃ意味がない... ない... ないんじゃない？
then doesn't that make it all... completely... meaningless?
I'm just spinning around, around, around, around the world
好きにキリがない... ない... ないから
Because there's no end... no end to doing as I please,
Spinning around, around, around, around the world
好きにもどかしい 想い 伝えたいから
because I want to convey these frustrating, passionate feelings.
トントン 軽快 トントン 届かない そんな I love you もありでしょう
Knock, knock, lively knock knock, it doesn't reach; even such an "I love you" must exist, right?
コンコン こんがらがって ほどけない 恋にミラクル起こすよ
Clunk, clunk, all tangled up and untangle-able; I'll work a miracle on this love!
神様 わたしが あなたの神様みたいね
Dear God, it seems like I am YOUR god, doesn't it?
Let Me Stay Here
[Song: Let Me Stay Here]
風と遊ぶ空に 青い小鳥たち ほほえんで歌おう 輪になり踊ろう
Blue birds in the sky playing with the wind, let's sing with a smile and dance in a ring.
Green tree and evergreen trees, 夢の続きで
Green tree and evergreen trees, in the continuation of a dream.
恋する魔法に かけられた 風にささめく妖精
A fairy whispering in the wind, cast under a spell of love.
ここは おやすみ ユニコーンの背中で
Sleep here, on the back of a unicorn.
高いお城の塔から シャボン玉 ほどけてね
Soap bubbles floating down from the high castle tower, unraveling gently.
お星さま
Dear stars...
It's just a fairy tale, so it won't go away like a lollipop.
Riding by, well...
Blending right now, in the light... ねぇ お願い ねぇ Let me stay here
Blending right now, in the light... Hey, please, hey, let me stay here.
Ring a ring o' roses, fa la la, round and round, fa la la la
Fall in the pit down, fa la la, I wanna stay here forever
Fall in the pit down, fa la la, ここに来て
Fall in the pit down, fa la la, come here to me...
時計の針... 止めて
and stop... the hands of the clock.
お星さまと はにかんでキス
A shy kiss with the stars...
ふたりは いつまでも 幸せに暮らしました
And the two lived happily ever after.
But it was just my dream, the golden sunlight shows it's time to wake up.
Waiting quietly, shutting my eyes and I say: "お願い、もっと Let me stay here"
Waiting quietly, shutting my eyes and I say: "Please, let me stay here longer."
バニラ ソルトで バニラ ソルトで
Vanilla salt, vanilla salt
バニラ
Vanilla
甘い
If it's sweet...
だけなら
...and nothing else,
ソルト
...then let's add...
かけましょう
...a sprinkle of salt!
誰よりももっともっと
More than anyone else,
私を知ってほしいから曝け出したい
I want you to know me, so I want to expose it all.
でもできないの 経験ナッシング
But I can't, I have zero experience.
もどかしすぎる
It's so frustrating!
弱さ見せようとすればするほど
The more I try to show my weakness,
無駄に強がりすべてが裏腹
the more I act tough, making everything turn out opposite.
本当は私 泣き虫なんだ
Honestly, I'm just a crybaby,
黙っていたけど
though I kept quiet about it.
でも甘いだけの愛はちょっと
But love that's only sweet is a bit...
私が求めているものとは違う
...different from what I'm looking for.
「嫌い」と言われたら
If you tell me "I hate you,"
「黒」だって言っちゃう
I end up saying "It's black!"
素直になれない
I can't be honest,
甘の天邪鬼
a sweet contrarian.
「好き」と言われたら
If you tell me "I love you,"
「大嫌い」だって
I say "I hate you so much!"
嬉しいのに何でなんだろう
Even though I'm happy, why am I like this?
甘い
Just like...
バニラに
...sprinkling salt...
ソルト
...onto sweet...
かけるように
...vanilla.
一途に好きになってしまったな
I really fell for you so devotedly.
24時間なの？ ずっと
Is it 24 hours a day? Constantly...
あなたのことをひたすら I think
All I do is think of you.
かなり極端
It's pretty extreme!
まさかここまであなたにはまると
I never expected to fall for you this hard.
誰も予想なんてしていなかった
No one could have ever predicted it.
天気予報じゃ当たらないんだ
Even weather forecasts can't predict...
恋の行方は
...where love will go.
ふたりで一緒にいる時間に
In the time we spend together,
刻まれた思い出は宝物なんだ
the memories carved are my true treasures.
「右」と言われたら
If you tell me "Go right,"
「左」に曲がっちゃう
I turn to the left.
素直になれない
I can't be honest,
甘の天邪鬼
a sweet contrarian.
「好き」と言われたら
If you tell me "I love you,"
「大嫌い」だって
I say "I hate you so much!"
嬉しいのに何でなんだろう
Even though I'm happy, why am I like this?
バニラ
Vanilla...
甘いだけのバニラより
Rather than just sweet vanilla,
ちょっと塩したほうが
adding a little salt...
甘みも増していくしね
...makes the sweetness even richer,
飽きがこない
so you never get tired of it.
甘いだけの愛もそう
It's the same for a love that's only sweet.
ちょっと塩したほうが
Adding a little salt...
ふたりの距離も縮まり
...brings the two of us closer,
きっと今日より素敵な未来が待ってるの
and a future even better than today awaits us.
「嫌い」と言われたら
If you tell me "I hate you,"
「黒」だって言っちゃう
I end up saying "It's black!"
素直になれない
I can't be honest,
甘の天邪鬼
a sweet contrarian.
「好き」と言われたら
If you tell me "I love you,"
「大嫌い」だって
I say "I hate you so much!"
嬉しいのに何でなんだろう
Even though I'm happy, why am I like this?
甘い
If it's sweet...
だけなら
...and nothing else,
ソルト
...salt!
かけましょう
Let's sprinkle it,
バニラソルトで
With vanilla salt,
with vanilla salt,
バニラソルトで
with vanilla salt.
Ah, thank you for listening!
Ooh, that song brings back memories!
Vanilla Salt from Toradora! We did... did a Members' Watchalong of that together!
So that song is special to me. It always brings back memories, and makes me a little bit emo.
But maybe I'm always emo inside.
I don't know, there's something about... about songs having memories attached to them...
It brings out the feels. But maybe it's also this beautiful place that brings out the feels.
Or maybe it's you that brings out the feels!
Did you like the songs I chose?
I really wanted to go for things... or songs that had like a soft effect to them.
And I was happy to be able to sing some of my favorite songs for you.
I wonder if you've heard all of them.
Do you know... do you know where they're all from? They're all from anime!
But I was happy to sing them,
and I was especially happy to be able to perform with Watame and Gura as well!
So thank you two for performing with me!
And thank you, you guys, because it's because of you that I'm able to stand here like a true idol!
And look, I changed! I changed from before! I'm wearing my idol outfit now!
It's really pretty! I especially love when it glows like this.
I think it matches the nighttime ambience perfectly.
And I really feel like a magical princess!
Because... because look! Come here, come here!
Let me bless you with my sparkles!
Doesn't it feel magical? I really love it!
And I really love the nighttime version of the stage. It has completely transformed!
I might be a little biased, I think I like the nighttime version better.
It has these glowing orbs in the forest.
I really wanted it to have a magical feel.
And it has beautiful glowing flowers... there might even be some glowing mushrooms!
You think they're poisonous? Will you check for me?
No no, don't do that! It's too dangerous.
Plus, I don't like eating mushrooms. Do you like them?
Have Saplings learned to take all of my habits for their own yet?
But I think on this stage, we also have... perhaps you've seen...
Dancing Saplings! Look at you, aren't you cute?
And they each have their own personalities. You all do.
Which one is you? Is that you? That you?
And the stage has also transformed the gazebo! Now instead of a tea party, we have this bed,
which perhaps I will collapse on after this is done.
Ugh, so sleepy!
I need to hang in there a little more! Send me your energy!
But actually, wouldn't I... wouldn't I go sleep in my beautiful cottage in the background?
Maybe... maybe this is where the Saplings sleep! Saplings have to sleep outside.
At least I gave you a nice... nice bed to sleep on in a nice gazebo!
What do you think? Do you like the daytime version or the nighttime version? I'm a fan of the nighttime version myself.
Well, I do have one more thing to show you in this stream. Can you guess what it is?
It would be... dun dun dun dun dun!
Wah, it's merch!
I have more merch for you!
I wanted to make something that would be really useful.
And earlier this year, when I came to Japan for the first time, I discovered phone rings.
They're a magical invention! They changed my life.
It's starting to sound like an infomercial here.
No, you cannot skip the ad!
No skip ad!
Um, if you're not familiar with the concept of a phone ring, basically...
...you stick it on the back of your phone, any phone,
and then you can use it to prop up your phone anywhere you go,
and watch YouTube, watch me on YouTube, maybe.
Or whatever else you want.
Um, it's super useful to have a little stand,
and it also can help you hold your phone, too.
You can stick your fingers and it makes it more comfortable.
You don't want to strain your pinky, do you?
So that is the merch that I have created for you.
I hope you'll find it useful. It is in the shape of a cute golden apple...
...with a cute Sapling. There's kind of a Sapling theme.
It makes sense, because all of this is possible because of you guys.
Thank- Thank you.
Cute Saplings around, cute Sap...
...Sap Ring, phone ring...
I hope you'll like it. I hope you'll find it as useful as I have found it.
I hope it'll be useful merch for you.
And, so with that, I'm afraid...
...that our time is just about up.
But again, I really wanted to thank you.
You for being here, and watching, and cheering me on.
I'm just- I'm just a gaming Kirin.
But because of you, I can also be an idol!
And it has been a really magical experience...
...here in my forest. I'm glad you can finally see.
Finally see where I've been streaming all this time.
Closet- Closet is... is over there.
That's where- That's where I'm streaming for you.
Finally revealed.
Thank you... thank you,
from the bottom of my heart, for coming today! I appreciate it!
Because of you, I can be here and be an idol and... a gamer!
And live out my dreams! Thank you! Thank you!
And please don't forget to watch the other Council members' 3D showcases!
And watch IRyS's too, even if it was a while ago!
And I... want to...
Thank you, thank you, thank you! I can't say it enough!
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you...
...for watching! And...
...I will see you very soon. I appreciate you.
Thank you for being here. I hope you had a good time,
and I will see you next time!
Faunwell! Bye-bye!
Bye!
Ceres Fauna 3D Showcase #3DKirin